Guide to the Records of John Brademas Speeches 1965-1991 RG 3.0.10 RG 3.0.10
New York University Archives
- Series I
  - Helen Frankenthaler Presentation, NY, NY, (Helen Frankenthaler), Jan 6, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Starr Foundation/Nussenzweig Press Conference, NYU, (JB Moderates Press Conference), Jan 7, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Highlights of the Presidency at New York University, NYU, (NYU Achievements), Jan 10, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Symposium on Budget Balance, NY, NY, (Federal Budget), Jan 10, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Friends of Nancy Hanks, NY, (Nancy Hanks), Jan 13, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - SCE Paul McGhee Medal Lecture & Dinner, NYU, (Continuing Ed. & SCE), Jan 13, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - PH Dinner for Dean Ed Kaufman, NYU, (JB Brief Welcome), Jan 16, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Puerto Rico Residence Center Commencement, San Juan, PR, (Education), Jan 18, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - IFA Board Meeting, NYU, (NYU Status), Jan 29, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Center for National Policy Lecture by Edmund S. Muskie, NYU, (Introduction-Edward Muskie), Jan 30, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - General Talking Points for Palm Beach, Florida, Palm Beach, FL (General Talking Points), Feb 1, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - First All-University Florida Alumni Day Brunch, Hollywood, FL, (Fundraising Brunch), Feb 2, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Corrigan Dinner, NYU, (JB Welcoming Remarks), Feb 5, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - JB Draft Press Release on FY 87 Budget, NYU, (Budget Effects on Education), Feb 7, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Executive Committee of the Board of Trustees, NYU, (NYU Status), Feb 10, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Dinner for Margaret Atwood, NY, NY, (Short Remarks on Atwood), Feb 12, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Wilson Draft, NY, NY, (Position Paper on Education), Feb 13, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Urban Research Center Press Conference, NYU, (JB Welcome), Feb 24, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Metro Center Benefit Lunch, NYU, (Value of Metro Center to NYC, Importance of Corporate Support for Its Programs), Feb 25, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - NYU Magazine Essay, NYU, (JB Introduces Magazine), Mar 1, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Annual Report Statement, NYU, ("Building Toward the 21st Century: The Challenges of Higher Education), Mar 1, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Afternoon at Washington Square, NYU, (Liberal Arts Education), Mar 2, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Medical Center Board of Trustees Meeting, NYU, (Medical Center Condition), Mar 4, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Great Artists Series Honoring Louise Nevelsol, NY, NY, Mar 5, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - International Relations Study Center, NYU, (Congress Role in Making Foreign Policy), Mar 5, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - National Book Critics Circle Awards Ceremony, NYU, (JB Welcome), Mar 6, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Introduction of President Gerald Ford/BPA Conference, NYU, (JB Introduction), Mar 7, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - International Celebration '86 Lecture, NYU, (International Education Programs at NYU), Mar 10, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Presidential, University & Education Scholars Breakfast, NYU, (JB Welcome), Mar 11, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Briefing for the NY Delegation, Washington DC (Reagan Budget Effects), Mar 12, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - New York University Senate, NYU, (NYU Condition), Mar 13, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Association for Children & Adults with Learning Disabilities International Conference, NY, NY, (Federal Support of Disabled), Mar 13, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - 33rd Annual GBA Business Conference, NYU, (JB Brief Remarks), Mar 15, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - NYU Board of Trustees, NYU, (NYU Condition), Mar 17, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - 16th Annual Real Estate Insititute Urban Leadership Award Dinner, NY, NY (Francil L. Bryant, Jr. Receives Award), Mar 19, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Visiting USIA Educators Group, NYU, (JB Breif Welcome), Mar 24, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Triangle Fire Memorial Rally, NYU, (Memorial Ceremony), Mar 25, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - The Third Olive Branch Awards Ceremony, NY, (JB Brief Welcome), Mar 25, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - TSOA Press Luncheon, NYU, (Yuri Lyubimov & Zelda Fichandler are Honored), Mar 26, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Mayor's Press Conference on SEHNAP, NYU, (Communication Skills Project), Mar 26, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Medical Center Board of Trustees Annual Meeting, NYU, (Medical Center Condition), Apr 1, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Screening of "Spain: Ten Years After…", NYU, (JB Welcome), Apr 2, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Trip to Florence, Italy, Florence, Italy, (JB Talking Points), Apr 3, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Presentation of the C. Walter Nichols Award to Felix Rohatyn, NYU, (JB Reads Conferment), Apr 3, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Touro College Convocation, Huntington, NY, (Law Profession), Apr 13, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Lunch for Westchester Guidance Counselors, NYU, (NYU Attractions), Apr 14, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Constatine Trypanis Dinner, NYU, (JB Presents Inaugural Award), Apr 15, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Senate Meeting, NYU, (NYU Affairs), Apr 17, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Founders Day Honors Convocation, NYU, (Remark to Honorees), Apr 17, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Washington D.C. All-University Alumni Branch, Washington, DC (Blurbs on NYU Schools), Apr 18, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Library of Congress Symposium, Washington, DC, ("Scholarship & Public Policy"), Apr 18, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - GPA Dean's Day/Intro Moynihan, NYU, (Alumni Remarks, Intro of Marnold Fellows Program & Moynihan), Apr 19, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Luncheon for Roger Penrose, NYU, (Intro of Penrose), Apr 23, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - A Nation at Risk Conference, Salt Lake City, UT (Higher Education), Apr 26, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Davie Forum Public Lecture, San Francisco, CA ("The Values of Higher Education"), Apr 28, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Alerdinck East-West Media Conference IV, 703 Main Bldg., (JB Remarks on "Between the Summits"), May 2, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - NYU-Alerdinck Conference/Lunch, NYU, (Soviet Union/USA Journalism), May 2, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - 25-Year Service Awards, NYU, (JB Brief Remarks), May 5, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Notre Dame Alumni Club of NY Dinner, NY, NY (Needs of Higher Education), May 6, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - National Commission on Excellence in Educational Administration New York Seminar, NYU, (JB Welcoming Remarks), May 8, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - University Senate, NYU, (NYU Affairs), May 8, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Annual Connerece/BPA Dinner, NYU, (Brief Remarks), May 8, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Henry R. Ferrettie Memorial Dinner, Mishawaka, IN (Federal Funding of Education), May 10, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, NYU, (NYU Affairs), May 12, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - Testimony at a Hearing of the Subcommittee on Select Revenue Measures of the Committee on Ways & Means, Washington, DC (Faculty Housing), May 12, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Spanish Civil War Symposium, NYU, (Brief Remarks), May 14, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - Annual Heights Colleges Awards Dinner, NYU, (Brief Remarks), May 16, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - Avery Fisher Center Dedication, NYU, (Avery Fisher), May 19, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - Leo Jaffe Theatre Dedication, NYU, (Leo Jaffe), May 21, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - Annual Dinner Meeting for the New York Alliance for the Public Schools, NYU, (New York Alliance), May 27, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Trustees Dinner, NYU, (Honorary Degree Recipeints), Jun 4, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - NYU Commencement, NYU, (JB Intro of Speaker O'Neill, Remarks to Alumni, Students Tisch Remarks), Jun 5, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - School of Medicine Commencement, NYU, (Federal Funding for Medical Education), Jun 5, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - Intro. Of Gov. Dukakis, NY, NY, Jun 6, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - Scholarship Winner of SCE's "Summer Writers Conference", NYU, (JB Welcome), Jun 10, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - Forum on State Economic Development Policy, NYU, (Urban Research Center), Jun 17, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 92)
  - NYU Reception for University Athletic Association, NYU, (JB Welcome), Jun 23, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - GPA Conference for Health Mgrs., NYU, (International Education), Jun 30, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 94)
  - Art News Magazine Interview, NY, NY (Washington Square Arch), Jun 30, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Commentary for Social Ed., NY, NY (Federal Support of Education), Jul 2, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - Liberty Weekend Conference, NY, NY (Liberty), Jul 6, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 97)
  - PH Dinner for Chinese Presidents, NYU, (JB Welcome), Jul 10, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 98)
  - Essay on Education in 2011 A.D., NY, NY (Future of Education), Jul 22, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 99)
  - Salzberg Seminar, Salzburg, Austria, (Congress & Foreign Policy), Aug 12, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 100)
  - Harvard Symposium on Liberal Learning, Cambridge, MA (Liberal Arts), Sep 3, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 101)
  - Harvard-Epworth Church Sermons, Cambridge, MA (Religion & Politics), Sep 7, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 102)
  - Background Material for Meeting with Ned Schnurman, NY, NY (Changing Student Attitudes), Sep 8, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254675
  - Washington Square Park Meeting, NY, NY (Welcoming Remarks), Sep 9, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Student Convocation, NYU, (Remarks to New Students), Sep 15, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Brookings Institute Conference, Washington, DC ("The Value of Public Service"), Sep 16, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Breakfast at the Regency Hotel, NY, NY (JB Intro Terry Sanford), Sep 16, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Aquino Lecture, NYU, (Cory Aquino Lecture), Sep 19, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Lotos Club Dinner, NY, NY, (JB Receives Award), Sep 22, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee Meeting/Board of Trustees, NYU, (NYU Affairs), Sep 22, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Alumni Council Meeting, NYU, (JB Welcoming Remarks), Sep 22, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - GBA Overseers Dinner, NYU, (JB Brief Remarks), Sep 25, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Franklin Pierce College, Rindge, NH, ("The Value of Liberal Arts"), Sep 27, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - NYC School Volunteer Program (Public Schools), NY, NY (Federal Support of Education), Sep 30, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Medical Center Board of Trustees, NYU, (NYU Affairs), Oct 2, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Nancy Hanks Dedication, Washington, DC (Personal Tribute/Nancy Hanks), Oct 6, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - NYU Senate Meeting, NYU, (Development, Admissions, Facilities, Asbestos, Drugs, Security, South Africa), Oct 9, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Sir Curtis Keeble Dinner, NYU, (Sir Curtis Keeble), Oct 15, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Breakfast for NYU Orienatation Leaders, NYU, (Thank You to Students), Oct 16, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - 127th Annual Session of the American Dental Association, Miami Beach, FL (Dental Education), Oct 19, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Florida Alumni Leader Organizational Luncheon, Miami Beach, FL (State of NYU), Oct 19, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - The Board of Trustees, NYU, (Development, Admissions, Facilities, Tax Bill), Oct 20, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - NYU Dentist Alumni in Florida, Miami Beach, FL (Alumni Activities), Oct 20, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Press Conference for Temporary Closing of Washington Square Park, Washington Square Park, (Park Cleanup), Oct 22, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - "Is the Agenda for Science Too Important to be Left to Scientists?", Washington DC, (Sixma XI Centennial Meeting), Oct 25, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - NYSERNET Press Conference, NYU, (Announcement of New High-Speed Communications Network), Oct 28, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Interview with Al Scardino of NYT, (NYU Board of Trustees), Oct 29, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - "The American Economy: The Political Dimension", 92nd St. Y, (Economic Politics), Oct 29, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Dedication for the William S. & Frances B. Todman Center for Film & Television, NYU, (Tisch School of Arts, Fran Todman), Oct 30, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Dental School Fall Alumni Day, NYU, (Dental School), Oct 31, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - BPA Charles Wald Haskins Dinner Honoring John C. Whitehead, NY, NY (John C. Whitehead), Nov 5, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - IFA Board Meeting, NYU, (Development, Tax Bill, Foundations), Nov 5, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Tribute to Louis Koenig, (JB Letter), Nov 7, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - The Fulbright Alumni Association of Greater New York, NY, NY (International Education), Nov 8, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - NYU Parent's Day, NYU, (NYU), Nov 9, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Grantmakers in the Arts Second National Conference, NY, NY (Federal Funding of the Arts), Nov 12, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Sir Ernst Gombrich Lecture, NYU, (Intro of Sir Ernst Gombrich), Nov 17, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - PH Dinner/GSAS 100th Anniversary, NYU, (Honorary Degree Recepients), Nov 19, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - GSAS 100th Anniversary Convocation, NYU, (Honorary Degrees to: Helen Ahrweiler, Sir Ernst Gombrich, Maestro Andres Secobia, Victor F. Weisskopg), Nov 19, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - "Tax Reform in America: The Impact on Higher Education", Jersey City, NJ (Business Symposium Sponsored by St. Peter's College), Nov 19, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - BPA-GBA Board of Overseers, NYU, (Business Programs), Nov 20, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Scanlan Dinner, Nov 25, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Kinnock Dinner, Dec 1, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Saul Bellow Introduction, NYU, (Saul Bellow), Dec 4, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Sports & Recreation Committee Meeting, NYU, (JB Brief Remarks), Dec 5, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Meeting of the Board of Trustees, NYU, (Research Caucus, Facilities, Special Events), Dec 8, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Scholarship & Public Policy Humanities Council, (Essay on Federal Support of Higher Education), Dec 9, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Department of Hebrew & Judaic Studies PH Dinner, NYU, (JB Brief Remarks), Dec 11, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Meeting of the Univeristy Senate, NYU, (Research Caucus, Facilities, Special Events, Dept. of Hebrew & Judaic Studies), Dec 11, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - New York Times Interview,(Claire Flom & the Alliance), Dec 11, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - "Meanwhile Greece Goes on Travelling…". Cambridge, MA (International Education), Dec 12, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - PH Dinner for Major Donors, NYU, (Brief Remarks), Dec 16, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - NY Public Library Lecture, NY, NY (Scholarship & Public Policy), Jan 6, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Meeting for the NYU Medical Center Board of Trustees, NYU, (Development, Washington, DC), Jan 6, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Highlights of the Presidency of John Brademas, Jan 10, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Forbes Response to Article by Peter Brimelow. (Higher Education), Jan 23, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Sigma Xi of Terre Haute Reception, Terre Haute, IN (Science), Jan 26, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - "Scholarship of Public Policy", Terre Haute, IN, (Address on Scholarship & Public Policy), Jan 26, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Message from Dr. Brademas for Staff Handbook, (Short Intro), Jan 27, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - "The Role of Congress in Foreign Policy: Reflections of a Former Congressman", Terre Haute, IN, (Lecture on Congress & Foreign Policy), Jan 27, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Indiana State University Founder's Day Remarks, Terre Haute IN, (Liberal Arts), Jan 27, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Institute of Fine Arts Board Meeting, NYU, (Faculty, NYU Happenings), Jan 28, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - National Book Critics Circle Awards Ceremony, NYU, (JB Brief Welcoming Remarks), Jan 29, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - WABC Talk Radio Interview, NY, NY, (Reach for Speech Program), Feb 1, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Journal of Int'l Law & Politics Symposium: Trade Sanctions & Int'l Relations, NYU, (JB Opening Remarks), Feb 5, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - National Association of Independent Colleges & Universities, Washington, DC, ("National Priorities in Higher Education"), Feb 6, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Executive Comm. Meeting of Board of Trustees, NYU, (Current State of NYU), Feb 9, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Cong. Testimony - Comm. Ed & Labor, Washington, Feb 10, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Citizens Comm. - New Yorker for NY Awards, NY, NY (JB Receives Award), Feb 12, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Senate Meeting, NYU, (Current State of NYU), Feb 12, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Sigma Xi Article for American Scientist, ( "Is the Agenda for Science Too Important To Be Left To Scientist?"), Feb 15, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Consulate-General of the People's Republic of China, NY, NY (Short Remarks on China), Feb 17, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Democratic National Committee National Finance Council, Newport Beach, CA (Ed. & Competitiveness), Feb 21, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - NYU AIDS Mental Health Project Press Conference, NYU, (JB Moderator), Feb 24, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Italian Minister Spadolini, NYU, (JB Intro), Feb 25, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - 2nd Annual Petrie Lecture in Entrepreneurship & PH Dinner, NYU, (Center for Entrepreneurial Studies), Feb 26, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Article for Education Record, ("International Education: A Matter of Survival", Feb 27, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - University Article on JB in Oxford, Mar 1987 (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - Medical Center Board, NYU, ( Current State of Med. Center), Mar 3, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - Lunch for Peter Lax, NYU, (JB MC for Lunch), Mar 1987 (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - David Kriser Dinner, NY, NY (Current State of NYU), Mar 4, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - Afternoon at Washington Square, NYU, (Importance of Liberal Arts Ed.), Mar 8, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - NYU in Albany Alumni Reception, Albany, NY (Alumni Efforts, State of NYU), Mar 9, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - Metro Center Benefit Luncheon, NYU, (Metro Center), Mar 10, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 82)
  - Presidential, University & Ed. Scholars Breakfast, NYU, (JB Greets Students), Mar 10, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - NY Historical Society, NY, NY "(NY: University in the City"), Mar 11, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 84)
  - Association of the Bar Forum, NY, NY ("Modern Role of Congress"), Mar 12, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 85)
  - University Senate Meeting, NYU, (NYU), Mar 12, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 86)
  - NYU Board of Trustees, NYU, (NYU), Mar 16, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 87)
  - Arms Control Forum, NYU, (JB Intro. Cuomo), Mar 16, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 88)
  - Press Conference for "Due Case", NYU, (JB Short Remarks), Mar 16, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 89)
  - GPA Dean's Day, NYU, (GPA), Mar 16, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 90)
  - Lynne Cheney Press Conf., NYU, (Lunch & Dinner for NEH Chairman), Mar 16, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 91)
  - Dinner Honoring Lady Warnock Commonwelath Fund Dinner, NYU, (Value of Int'l Exchanges), Mar 17, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 92)
  - Real Estate Institute Leadership Award Dinner, NYU, (Award to Larry Tisch), Mar 18, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 93)
  - Hoosiers Dinner, NYU, (Movie "Hoosiers"), Mar 19, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 94)
  - Chicago & Los Angeles Alumni Rec., Chicago, LA (NYU), Mar 26, 1987-Mar 29, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254683
  - Onassis Center For Hellenic Studies Convocation,NYU, (JB Remarks for Press Conf. Luncheon, Convocation Dinner), Mar 30, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Humanities Book Essay, NYU, ("Scholarships & Public Policy"), Apr 1, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - NY Academy of Sciences, NYC, (Future of Science Ed in America), Apr 1, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - NY Science Policy Association, New York, NY (Federal Support of Science), Apr 1, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Testimony Before Committee on Gov't Affairs, Washington, DC, (Education & Competitiveness), Apr 2, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - New England Alumni Brunch, Boston, (Alumni Speech), Apr 5, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Gerald Aylmer Lecture & Dinner, NYU, (JB Intro Aylmer & Talking Points), Apr 6, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - ACE Letter - Saunders (Letter Re: Draft Prop. of Nat'l Chall. in Higher Education), Apr 7, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Medical Center Board of Trustees, NYU, (Medical Center Affairs), Apr 7, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - NYU Senate, NYU, (NYU Affairs), Apr 9, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Stephen J., Sr. & Beatrice Brademas Lecture, Muncia, Ind., (Intro. Lee Hamilton), Apr 13, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Greek Fulbright Alumni Assoc., Greece, (Brief Greetings), Apr 28, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Fulbright Distingusished Fellows Lecture, Greece,("Fulbright at 40: Forging the Ties that Bind"), Apr 29, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - American School of Classical Studies Dinner, Greece, (Brief Greetings), Apr 30, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - "Message from the President" For Staff & Faculty Handbooks, NYU, (Short Remarks to New Employees), May 4, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - University of Athens, Greece,(University & Values), May 4, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - IFA Board Meeting, NYU, (General Events at Washington Square/Trip to Greece), May 6, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - 20th Annual Conf. on the NYC Economy, NYC, ("Facing the Competition in Brainpower"), May 6, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - President's Council Reception, NYU, (Importance of Unreistricted Giving/State of NYU), May 7, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Notre Dame Speech, Notre Dame, (Value of Private Higher Ed. & the Need for Support for Private Colleges & Univ's), May 9, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - PH Dinner for TS0A, NYU, (JB Talking Points), May 11, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Dedication of Paulette Goddard Staircase, NYU, (JB Brief Remarks on Goddard), May 11, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Board of Trustees, NYU, (NYU Affairs), May 11, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - NY Academy of Public Education, NYC, (JB Recieves Award), May 12, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Wagner Labor Dinner, NYU, (Awards Presented to Labor Leaders for their Support of the Archives), May 13, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Leonary Stern Hall Dedication, NYU, (Dedication Ceremony for Stern), May 14, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - NYU Senate, NYU, (NYU Affairs), May 14, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Humanities Council Symposium, NYU, (JB Brief Remarks), May 15, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Washington D.C. Alumni Brunch, Washington, DC, (Alumni Speech), May 17, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Bobst Awards in Arts & Letters, NYU, (Honorary Degrees to: John Updike, Flora Lewis, Louis Simpson, Harold Acton), May 19, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - 25 Year Service Awards, NYU, (JB Presents Awards), May 20, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Foreign Broadcasters Seminar, NYU, (Greetings to Broadcasters), May 21, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - NYU Community Fund, NYU, (JB Presents Checks to Community Funds), May 21, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Gallatin Association Leadership Breakfast, NYC, (Private Giving, Recent NYU Developments), May 27, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Alumni Council Annual Meeting, NYU, (Report on University), May 28, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Walter Nichols Award to James D. Robinson III, NYU, (Award Presentation), May 29, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - United Jewish Appeal, NYC, (Higher Ed., Threats to Philanthropy), Jun 1, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - GBA Pre-Commencement, NYU, (Presidential Citation to Dr. Kobayashi), Jun 2, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Medical Center Board of Trustees, NYU, (Medical Center Issues), Jun 2, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - NY Congressional Delegation, Washington, DC, (Higher Ed, NYU Programs Related to Public Service), Jun 3, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Trustees Dinner, NYU, (Honorary Degree Recipients), Jun 4, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Educational Press Association, Washington, DC, (Higher Education), Jun 4, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 43)